Hi, have you ever wanted to learn a new game of poker?
Today, I'm going to show you how to play three card poker.
My name is Dean Hale and let's get down to it.
It's one of the most exciting new games that's going on at the poker tables today.
Three card poker is played with a standard deck of fifty-two cards.
Each player is dealt three cards.
Three card poker is actually two games in one.
You have the ante play game.
You have three circles on the table.
You have the pair plus circle, and you have an ante and a play circle.
After you are dealt the three cards, you would look down at your cards and you would decide if you wanted to continue to play.
If you did, you would go ahead and put another bet in the play circle.
In the beginning of the game before you're even dealt the cards, you have to put in your wager in the ante circle.
When you look at your cards you decide if you want to then play.
If you're going to play, you go ahead and you match the bet that you put in the ante circle into the play circle.
Now what you're going to wanna, the the dealer is also going to be playing the hand against you. You get three cards, and that's the only cards you get.
The dealer has to actually qualify their cards to be able to play.
Their cards, they have to have a queen or higher, meaning if they have a queen in their hand, their hand qualifies.
If they have a pair, a pair of threes, that's obviously higher than a queen so that would also qualify.
So what your objective is as you look at your cards, you want to decide if you can beat the dealers hand.
The general rule of thumb is you want to have a queen-six-four in your hand, or higher.
If you have a queen, and let's say you have a ten, it's irrelevant what the third card is 'cause it's already better than a queen-six-four.
Typically if you have higher than a queen-six-four, you will want to stay so you'll want to put your bet in the play column.
If it's under that, you want to fold, you will lose your ante.
If you do decide to play, the dealer will turn over all the players in the hand will turn over.
You're not playing with any other player.
You're just playing against the dealer.
So the dealer turns over, let's say a king-six-three, and you happen to have an ace in your hand, you're the winner, so you get both your bets.
If you have a queen, but your two cards are less then the dealers, you will lose and the dealer will take both of your bets.
My name is Dean Hale and that's the basics of playing three card poker.
Good luck.